hotelscan.com 2019-06-04

# Privacy Policy | hotelscan

### Privacy is important.

We believe that any person should feel safe and protected online, that is why the privacy of our customers is so important to us. This Privacy Policy was created in order to explain what personal identifying data and information you may send via the Internet to our website (hereinafter the “Personal Data”), how it is protected and why we may use it. Since this Privacy Policy regulates protection and handling any Personal Data belonging to you, read it carefully please. By using our website to find the lowest price for hotel accommodations. you give consent to this Privacy Policy and agree to the collection and use of such Personal Data as set out in this Privacy Policy. Bravometa has the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time without individual, specific notice to you, and such modifications shall be effective immediately upon posting them on our Website.

### What do we do with data provided?

We may analyze collected Personal Data concerning online behavior, user preferences, approximate location, some technical issues, etc. We know it seems boring, but analytics help us to improve and optimize our services designed for you.

### Who can get it?

We don’t transmit Personal Data to third parties outside of Bravometa without your consent except when required to do so for legal or regulatory purposes and in cases herein. Personal Data may be transferred to third parties that act for or on behalf of us for further processing in accordance with the purposes for which it was originally collected.We shall ensure that such third parties provide the same level of protection as we have. Moreover, they will be contractually bound to process Personal Data only for the purposes authorized by you and on a confidential basis.

### How do we care about you?

We shall take all reasonable steps in order not to allow your Personal Data to be seen by third parties other than in cases hereunder.To ensure the security and confidentiality of Personal Data that we collect online, we use industry standard firewalls and other means of protection. Although we have tried to create a secure, reliable and trustworthy Website for our users, you should be aware that the internet is generally not regarded as a complete secure environment, and that therefore the confidentiality of the Personal Data provided by you or material transmitted via our Website or by e-mail cannot be guaranteed by us. Thus, we can not be responsible or liable for the security of your Personal Data whilst in transit via the internet to us. So you should always pay attention while being online.

### What else can you expect?

We will never spam. Spamming is defined as sending unsolicited e-mails, usually of commercial nature, in large numbers and repeatedly to individuals with whom the sender has had no previous contact or who have declined to receive such communications.On the other hand, we may inform you about news concerning our Website, if you wish of course. By the way, you will have the right to withdraw at any time.

### What about Facebook and other social networks?

We may establish our official pages on social networks. It’s a cool thing, but you should remember that third-party’s privacy policy is applied when you register and stay there.When you visit our Website that contains social plugins, your browser establishes a direct connection to third-party’s servers. We have no influence on the data gathered by the plugin and inform you according to our state of knowledge: the embedded plugins may provide social networks with the information that you have accessed over the corresponding page of our Website.

### You won’t sue us, will you?

All disputes arising out of or in connection with the relationship between Bravometa and you shall be governed by substantive Swiss law excluding the conflict of law rules.The courts of Switzerland shall have exclusive jurisdiction to decide all disputes arising under this Privacy Policy.

### Problem?

Should you have any queries or complaints about our compliance with this Privacy Policy, or if you wish to make any recommendations or comments to improve the quality of this Privacy Policy, please contact us under [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) . We will do our best to improve the protection and security of the Personal Data you provide to us.
